Contact

neenaannmary11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/neenavarghese-650657210 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Troubleshooting
Quality Assurance
Testing

Neena Varghese

Software Quality Assurance Analyst Canada

Summary

Software QA Analyst with extensive experience as Manual Tester and Service desk support roles. Good exposure of testing skills, implementation, troubleshooting and system support activities.

-Experience of working in the complete Software Testing Life Cycle involving Requirement Analysis, Test Planning, Test-case Development, Environment setup, Test Execution & Testing cycle closure

Experience

ABELSoft Inc.

Software QA Analyst

November 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Burlington, Ontario, Canada

- -Convert business requirements into test plans and test cases; prepare or maintaining documents
- -Design and execute manual test plans and test scripts for complete modules and/or workflows
- Researching, compiling and analyzing information as per business requirements
- -Work closely with software developers to develop test specifications and build test cases to rigorously test product functionality
- Manage workload or managing deadlines
- -Follow through with investigation of all potential product test failures Verify and validate bug fixes

DriverCheck Inc.

DC Agile Medical Administrator March 2021 - November 2021 (9 months)

- Booked and registered COVID-19 and flu vaccine appointments using COVAX and Amenda software
- Efficiently worked on data entry for patients upon completion of COVID-19 vaccination project

Ontario Ministry of Government and Consumer Services

Service Desk Analyst

March 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 6 months)

- -Supported customers having data connectivity issues, assisting with troubleshooting steps and rebooting of hardware.
- -Maintained composure and patience in face of difficult customer situations, applying escalation techniques and positive customer support.
- -Analyzed, prioritized, researched and solved IT problems to achieve complete resolution for customers with minimal productivity loss.
- -Developed, wrote and maintained detailed troubleshooting guide and knowledge base for use by other service desk staff and field service staff.
- -Routed tracked and managed client's service desk tickets from inception to close and documented issues and results.

Concentrix

Technical Support Specialist
June 2020 - October 2020 (5 months)

- -Responded to 75-100 inbound calls per day in high call volume environment
- -Escalated issues to the proper help desk associate when necessary and followed up on any escalated

issues, all within a timely manner

- -Worked as the Help Desk providing PC and Mobile support, diagnosing, troubleshooting and resolving
- client issues with hardware maintenance, installations and upgrades.
- -Ensure service delivered to our customers meets contractual Key Performance Indicator ('KPIs')

Traks Pro India

System Administrator/ Office Administrator November 2016 - September 2017 (11 months)

- -Perform invoice coding and submit invoices to corporate office for payment.
- -Maintain all required documentation that includes business continuity documentation and seating charts for office.
- -Identify strategies to improve services, systems and process.
- -Interact with callers regarding the training program and providing them admission for the crash courses

BNY Mellon

Software Quality Assurance Analyst May 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 5 months) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

- -Analyzed system functional requirements and derived test coverage based on available documentation and walk-through with subject matter experts
- -Creation of metrics and test status reporting, provided detailed analysis of test progress and results. Analyzed, tested and provided resolution for customer queries raised through incident ticket
- -Maintenance of UI automation scripts, functional scripting and data maintenance. Test and defect management in HP ALM11 and supported production operations and enhancements

Education

Cambrian College
Postgraduate Degree, Cloud computing (2018 - 2019)

Mahendra Institute of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Electronics and communications
engineering · (2011 - 2015)